{
  "preserveQuestionOrder": false,
  "preserveRoundOrder": false,
  "author": "arunaromatics",
  "questions": [
    {
      "category": "'General' Knowledge",
      "question": "Which of these car brands is NOT owned by General Motors?",
      "correct": "Jeep",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Buick",
        "Cadillac",
        "Chevrolet"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "'General' Knowledge",
      "question": "Which actor played Johnnie Gray in the 1926 silent comedy 'The General', inspired by an event during the American Civil War?",
      "correct": "Buster Keaton",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Charlie Chaplin",
        "Fatty Arbuckle",
        "Harold Lloyd"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "'General' Knowledge",
      "question": "A Secretary General of the UN has NEVER been from which of these countries?",
      "correct": "Finland",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Austria",
        "Egypt",
        "Ghana"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "'General' Knowledge",
      "question": "The General is a newspaper written in the language of Malayalam from which country?",
      "correct": "India",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Sri Lanka",
        "Malaysia",
        "Pakistan"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "'General' Knowledge",
      "question": "'I Am the Very Model of a Modern Major-General' is a song from which Gilbert and Sullivan work?",
      "correct": "The Pirates of Penzance",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "H.M.S. Pinafore",
        "The Yeomen of the Guard",
        "Iolanthe"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General 'Knowledge'",
      "question": "Which of the following is the opening line of the ABBA song 'Knowing Me, Knowing You'?",
      "correct": "No more carefree laughter",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "They passed me by",
        "If you change your mind",
        "Where are those happy days"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General 'Knowledge'",
      "question": "The British television channel 'BBC Knowledge' was closed in 2002 and replaced with which other channel?",
      "correct": "BBC 4",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "BBC 3",
        "BBC News",
        "BBC Parliament"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General 'Knowledge'",
      "question": "Which British department store recently abandoned its 'Never Knowingly Undersold' price pledge?",
      "correct": "John Lewis",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "TJ Hughes",
        "Marks and Spencer",
        "House of Fraser"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General 'Knowledge'",
      "question": "Which of these songs appears in the same musical as the song 'I Know Him So Well'?",
      "correct": "One Night in Bangkok",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Heaven On Their Minds",
        "Call Me Rusty",
        "Close Every Door"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General 'Knowledge'",
      "question": "Which of these actors did NOT star in the 1997 film 'I Know What You Did Last Summer'?",
      "correct": "Rei Hance",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Jennifer Love Hewitt",
        "Sarah Michelle Gellar",
        "Anne Heche"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Kn'owl'edge",
      "question": "Which of these people once played for the English football club nicknamed 'The Owls'?",
      "correct": "Chris Waddle",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "John Barnes",
        "Ian Wright",
        "Andy Cole"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Kn'owl'edge",
      "question": "Harry Potter sits his 'O.W.L' exams in which book?",
      "correct": "Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire",
        "Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince",
        "Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Kn'owl'edge",
      "question": "'The Big Powerful Owl', an 8 metre tall statue of an owl, is a tourist attraction in which Australian city?",
      "correct": "Canberra",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Melbourne",
        "Perth",
        "Brisbane"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Kn'owl'edge",
      "question": "The Owl City song 'Fireflies' was released in the same year as which of these other songs?",
      "correct": "Empire State of Mind",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Crank That (Soulja Boy)",
        "Party Rock Anthem",
        "Blurred Lines"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Kn'owl'edge",
      "question": "'An Occurance at Owl Creek Bridge' is a story by which American author?",
      "correct": "Ambrose Bierce",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Stephen Crane",
        "Ernest Hemmingway",
        "Jack London"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "'G'eneral 'K'nowledge",
      "question": "When Guz Khan came second in his series of 'Taskmaster', who won?",
      "correct": "Morgana Robinson",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Mike Wozniak",
        "Sarah Kendall",
        "Daisy May Cooper"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "'G'eneral 'K'nowledge",
      "question": "Which of these colours is NOT featured in the lyrics of the Mika song 'Grace Kelly'?",
      "correct": "Black",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Green",
        "Violet",
        "Blue"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "'G'eneral 'K'nowledge",
      "question": "Which of these English monarchs was born in the same century as Genghis Khan?",
      "correct": "Henry II",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "William II",
        "Edward II",
        "Richard II"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "'G'eneral 'K'nowledge",
      "question": "Chess grandmaster Garry Kasparov was born in which city, the host of the 2012 Eurovision Song Contest?",
      "correct": "Baku",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Moscow",
        "Kyiv",
        "Tel Aviv"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "'G'eneral 'K'nowledge",
      "question": "Gladys Knight recorded the theme song to which James Bond film?",
      "correct": "License to Kill",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "A View to a Kill",
        "Tomorrow Never Dies",
        "Die Another Day"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "According to the Electromagnetic Spectrum, which of these waves has the longest wavelength?",
      "correct": "Radio Waves",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Microwaves",
        "X-Rays",
        "Gamma Rays"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "The shortest verse in the King James Bible occurs shortly before which event?",
      "correct": "The Raising of Lazarus",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "The Transfiguration",
        "Jesus Walking on Water",
        "The Sermon on the Mount"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "The Mason-Dixon line does NOT mark part of the border of which of these states?",
      "correct": "New Jersey",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Delaware",
        "Maryland",
        "West Virginia"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "What first name links a painter born in Seville in 1599, and an Argentine footballer?",
      "correct": "Diego",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Lionel",
        "Francisco",
        "Pablo"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Which of these people has NEVER been a host of 'Robot Wars'?",
      "correct": "Robert Llewellyn",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Craig Charles",
        "Dara O'Briain",
        "Jeremy Clarkson"
      ]
    }
  ]
}